//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers
var questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "2 + 3?",
    answer: 5,
    options: [
      5,
      6,
      7,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "10 - 6?",
    answer: 4,
    options: [
      3,
      9,
      4,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:"5 * 10?",
    answer: 50,
    options: [
      60,
      45,
      55,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "7 - 3?",
    answer: 4,
    options: [
      4,
      8,
      1,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "9 * 10?",
    answer: 90,
    options: [
      80,
      90,
      88,
      100
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "10 * 1?",
    answer: 10,
    options: [
      11,
      10,
      1,
      100
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "16 - 10?",
    answer: 6,
    options: [
      10,
      9,
      6,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "6 - 3?",
    answer: 3,
    options: [
      5,
      10,
      88,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "1 + 9?",
    answer: 10,
    options: [
      8,
      10,
      7,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "11 * 2?",
    answer: 22,
    options: [
      77,
      22,
      11,
      2
    ]
  }
];
